munnamark.blogspot.com 2018-02-19

# Marks PC Solution: Privacy Policy

_This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which[Marks PC Solution](http://www.markspcsolution.com/) collects, stores, analyzes and disseminates information collected from visitors and users as well._  
_  
__  
__  
_

_**Personal Information**_

_We sometimes collect personal information from users in a variety of ways regarding activities, services, and resources we make available for them. Users can visit our site anonymously. We collect personal information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us for their own interests - contacting via Email, making comments etc. And they are never forced to supply any kind of personal information.  _  
_  
__  
_  
_  
_

_**Impersonal Information**_

_We may collect non-personal information about visitors regarding how do they interact with our site. Such information may include browser name, type of device, operating system, location, search query, referring site etc._  
_  
_

_  
__  
__**Browser Cookies**_

_  
__We may use cookies in order to enhance our performance. Marks PC Solution never collects any personal or sensitive information from users through cookies. They are only used for better[SEO](http://www.markspcsolution.com/search/label/SEO) and Advertising purpose. _  
_  
__Since we're using Blogger platform and AdSense Ads, Google uses cookies for Google  Analytics and AdSense _  
_  
__User may choose to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent through browser settings. If they use any such settings, some parts of the site may not work properly._

_  
__  
_  
_  
__**Using the Information**_

_[Marks PC Solution](http://www.markspcsolution.com/) may use the collected information for the following purposes:_

  * _To enrich our contents_

  * _To provide desired information_

  * _To improve customer service_

  * _To respond to visitors' queries, requests etc.  _

  * _To improve our products and services.  _

  * _To make overall improvement depending on customers' feedback._

**_Your Information is 100% Secured_**

_  
__You don't need to register or sign up to access the services offered by Marks PC Solution. So we don't need to use your account your information. But for the purpose of commenting, you must have an account on Google.  _  
_  
__Some services may require your account information. We will deal such services personally. In that case, we will reach a mutual agreement regarding how the information will be collected and how the benefits will be provided.  _  
_  
__  
_  
_  
_

_**Sharing Information**_

_Marks PC Solution never shares users' personal information with others. And we never store or sell sensitive information of the users. However, we may use some information for the purpose of -  _

  * _Making illustrations in our articles_

  * _Informing others about an issue/ problem_

_But we do this with care. We always try to protect the privacy of the users.  _

_  
__  
__**Online Newsletter  **_

_  
__We don't like to be included our newsletter in your spam list! That's why we never force you to subscribe in our mailing list. And we never send newsletter to the users without their permission.  _  
_  
__You will receive our newsletter/ notifications only if you[subscribe](http://feedburner.google.com/fb/a/mailverify?uri=MarksPcSolution). _

_**Advertising**_

_For the purpose of generating revenues, we're bound to place and display third party ads like Google AdSense or other Ad Networks. We try our best so that those advertisements don't bother the visitors while reading our articles.  _  
_  
__We always try to avoid any kind of explicit and harmful ads on our site. Though sometimes users may see ads which are against their views. That's why we try to improve ads  continuously. _  
_  
__If visitors click any ad displayed in[Marks PC Solution](http://www.markspcsolution.com/), we suggest them to do so with their own responsibility. We've no authority there. _  
_  
_

_**Changes to this Privacy Policy**_

_[Marks PC Solution](http://www.markspcsolution.com/) reserves the right to amend, modify and update this privacy policy as and when required. If we bring any major change to this policy, and if we think it's necessary to inform you about such change, we'll show notification in our homepage. _  
_  
__We highly recommend you frequently check this privacy page for any kind of update.  _

_**Your Acceptance of the Terms & Conditions**_

_By using our site, you confirm that you agree with our privacy policy and[terms & conditions](http://www.markspcsolution.com/p/terms-conditions.html) as well. If you have any query about our Privacy Policy or if you disagree with any point, please [contact us](http://www.markspcsolution.com/p/contact-info.html). Your suggestions will be appreciated . . ._  
_  
__  
__  
__**NB:** This policy has been last updated on September 11, 2015. No part of this policy can be copied, regenerated or published on another website without permission of the [Admin](https://plus.google.com/105788345941851448052). _  
_  
__  
__  
__  
_

#### _Stay with  [Marks PC Solution](http://www.markspcsolution.com/) . . . _
